Mohammad Awlad

Front-end Web Developer



Mdawladbdinfo@gmail.com

L +8801725385909 / +8801518456520

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mdawlad/

https://github.com/mdawlad29

https://awladhossain.netlify.app/



OBJECTIVES

I am a Front-end Developer and I love to do coding. I also counted myself as a dedicated and hardworking person. I created lots of successful websites that are fast, easy to use, and built with my best effort. I used HTML, CSS, CSS Framework and Library, JavaScript and JavaScript Framework also library and JavaScript wrapper and also to produce responsive websites and web apps that provide users the best and most appropriate experience suited to their device and browser.

EXPERIENCE

01/06/2023 - present

Front-end Developer (React), MARHABA LTD.

Work Description: With the development team, I worked on the Front-end to build web applications. Some of my projects link:

• Marhaba Ltd: marhaba.com.bd

Eagle Shop

15/05/2022 - 30/04/2023

Front-end Developer (React), NEXIS LTD.

Work Description: With the development team, I worked on the Front-end to build web applications. Some of my projects link:

Nexis Ltd: nexisltd.com

• HR Management System

School Management System

• Digital Menu

TECHNOLOGY SKILL

- ❖ Preferable: React.Js, Next Js, JavaScript, Tailwind, Material Ui, React-bootstrap, HTML-5, CSS-3
- ❖ Comfortable: Node js, Express js, MongoDB, React Native.
- ❖ Familiar with: Git, GitHub, VS Code, Figma, Netlify, Chrome Dev Tools, Heroku, Firebase.

PROJECTS

FOODY

- ❖ Technology used: Next.js, Tailwind.css, Material UI, ES6, HTML 5, CSS 3
- Preview link: https://vault-frontend-coral.vercel.app/
- Client Site link: https://github.com/mdawlad29/vault-frontend
- ❖ **Description:** Foody is a restaurant website through which one can know all information about a restaurant and can order food while sitting at the table.

DREAM TRAVEL COUNTRY

- ❖ Technology used: HTML 5, CSS 3, ES6, bootstrap, react-bootstrap, react.js
- ❖ Back-end Technology: Node.is, Express.is, MongoDB
- Preview link: https://tourism-eb29a.firebaseapp.com/
- ❖ **Description:** Welcome to our travel website! Plan and book your next adventure with ease. Our secure and user-friendly platform makes it simple to explore the world. Start your journey with us today!

INSTANCE REAL ESTATE

- ❖ Technology used: HTML 5, CSS 3, ES6, bootstrap, react-bootstrap, react.js
- Back-end Technology: Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB
- Preview link: https://instance-realestate.web.app/
- Client Site Link: https://github.com/mdawlad29/Instance-real-state
- Server Site Link: https://github.com/Md-Awlad/Instance-real-state-server-site
- ❖ Description: This is a real estate website through which you can book various types of Radisson hotels. And after receiving the service, you can review.

BANGLA PUZZLE

- ❖ Technology used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ES6, React.js, Tailwind.css,
- Preview link: https://bangla-puzzles.netlify.app/
- ❖ Client Site Link: https://github.com/mdawlad29/bangla-puzzle

BONDHU HEALTH CARE

- ❖ Technology used: HTML 5, CSS 3, ES6, react, tailwind
- Preview link: https://bondhuhealth.netlify.app/
- Client Site link: https://github.com/mdawlad29/Bondhu-Health
- ❖ Description: Welcome to our bondhu health care website! We offer a range of prevention services for depression, anxiety disorders, and eating disorders. Signup and log in with Google to access our secure platform, and book the services you need to start your journey to recovery.

ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENT SYSTEM

- ❖ Technology used: HTML 5, CSS 3, bootstrap, react-bootstrap, react.js, JavaScript, ES6, typewriter effect, react-typecial, react-reveal,
- Preview link: https://intelligentsystemsolution.netlify.app/
- Client Site link: https://github.com/mdawlad29/intelligentsystemssolutions
- ❖ Description: It is an artificial intelligence system that you can order to create software according to your needs. So all information is presented through this site.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer

Bhola Polytechnic Institute Bhola, Bangladesh 2017-2021

Passing Year: 2022